Hey, Rifleheads!
What's a guy gotta do to
get a little food in here?
Kars!
This man's mechanical!
You're von Stroheim!
Double shock!
This is spookier than meeting a ghost
in a dark cemetery after midnight!
Kars!
And von Stroheim,
who I could have sworn was blown
into little tiny bits back in Mexico!
They're both standing
right in front of me!
Shijima-no-soko-kara.
Meta-menu-sono-hasira-tachi.
I'm going to call you a love song.
I'm going to call
you a love song.
Cars!
And von Stroheim is here too!
His hand looks like it's made of metal,
and his face is wrapped
in some strange machinery.
The Germans must have been hiding this.
What incredible medical technology!
Could it be for some kind of military use?
I guess that's what saved your
miserable life, von Stroheim.
George, as you can see,
I'm back from hell.
Should I be happy about it?
When you get down to it,
he's not exactly a bad guy.
Except for the fact that
he's a damn German soldier.
And I don't like the way he struts around
like he's better than everyone else.
Still, I am a bit happy.
Why don't you make yourself at home on
the sofa and watch me while I do my work?
He's glaring at me.
He knows that I'm the one who
killed ACDC, and he hates me for it.
Even so... Kars!
Do you think I'm gonna just sit here
and let you try and psych me out?
Jojo, once I'm finished securing the
stone, I'm going to put an end to you.
It's too bad Wamu is still
off working in Greece.
I can't allow a Hamon user who was
able to beat ACDC to remain alive.
Tell me something, Kars.
Do you speak as a warrior, or are you
after something else, like revenge?
Pay attention.
You're fighting me.
I'm Zavon who is going to
be your final opponent.
No machine can stop me.
Is that right?
Arms of flesh and blood can't bend like
that, which means they are mechanical.
Now for Zavon.
Wait, he's...
His fingers squeeze at 1,950
kilograms per centimeter squared.
Almost twice San Viento's strength.
You utter fool!
German science is the finest in the world!
These arms have such great power,
they were constructed based on
the abilities of San Viento!
Unzocas!
We've calculated exactly
what we need to do to you?
In order to eliminate your power!
and leave you in desperate agony.
I'm going to pluck you like a chicken,
beat by beat, and take you apart
one square centimeter at a time.
Hey, Jojo, don't you dare even
think about feeling sorry for me.
My proud new form is the
very embodiment of the
ultimate peak of German
science and engineering.
You see, I'm not merely human, I'm more.
Take this, cars.
My machine gun can fire
600 rounds per minute and
slid through armor plating
like it was made of paper.
I'll whittle you down into
tiny pieces in no time at all.
His body's mechanical, too?
The hell was that?
It came from downstairs.
I swear the stone will be mine today.
Attempting to get it cost ACDC his life.
I refuse to allow his ultimate
sacrifice to have been in vain.
That light, the blade coming
out of his arm is glowing.
I can control light.
Behold, brilliant bone blade.
Impossible.
That blade is hardened bone and skin.
It shouldn't be able to
deflect bullets like that,
let alone slice them in half in mid-air.
His blade is amazing, but
why is it glowing like that?
I, I, I know that sound.
Upon seeing the blade up close, Von
Stroheim was able to understand its secret.
It didn't have a simple edge.
Rather, it had a rotating
blade moving at high speed.
Tiny, razor-sharp claws slid quietly
along the outer edge of the blade,
ready to shred anything in its path.
Each claw was flawlessly
polished to a mirror
-like finish and refracted
the faintest light,
making the blade look as though
it were glowing from within.
We can't win this!
At least not with my weapons or any
modern technology that I know of!
We can't defeat him!
And what was San Bind?
Nothing but a weak child,
a well-trained guard dog.
He couldn't even compare to us.
Now, I'll take that stone.
Kars, what the hell?
That ice-cold sheen across his face.
A blade that can cut bullets in midair.
There's no way I could ever block
that thing with only my bare hands.
Even if I could concentrate all
of my harmon into a single blow,
that blade would still
slice right through me.
To be perfectly honest, I
want to run away from here.
He's way too dangerous
to take on directly.
I can't think of any way to
get around that blade of his.
Then again, I can't just leave
and let him take the stone.
If he obtains the stone's power,
he'd become practically invincible.
I'd never be able to defeat him.
Damn it all.
I have to get my hands on Womu's Antidote.
Kars wants to kill me after all.
Why me?
Was this in my horoscope?
what is this what's in this pocket here
oh the red stone of asia i have waited
a long time for this 5 000 years and at
last the stone is mine not that i ever
doubted it would be it was destined to
fall into my hands cause just be patient
i'll kill you in a moment damn that bastard
but he really hates everything about me.
Letting him walk away with the stone
would mean the end for everyone.
Kars, you fool.
Don't think you've beaten me because
I'm not finished with you yet.
German science is the world's greatest.
I will beat you.
Von Stroheim, you idiot.
What do you think you're doing?
How can you sit there and
boast at a time like this?
Ultraviolet beams, activate!
It's the stone!
Huh? Oh, no!
The stone is sliding down the slope!
Ah, damn it, no!
We have to stop it!
The stone is sliding towards the cliff!
If it falls off, it could be lost forever!
what the hell look at this what
what happened in here cars happened
Jojo you have to go after the
stone grab it while you still can
damn he's catching up he's fast he's
focused on the stone like a laser
the way he keeps accelerating he must
be planning to grab the stone and
fall off the cliff he won't be able
to stop before he reaches the edge
damn it the The drop beyond that cliff
is at least several hundred meters.
With all his superior abilities,
Kars could survive the fall.
But it's as high as jumping off the
tallest skyscraper without a parachute.
It'd be certain death for me.
He's passing me.
Jojo plans to slow down before he reaches
the edge so he doesn't go flying off,
but not Kars.
Jojo can't win.
There's no way I'm gonna let this
slime get his hands on the stone.
Go, run hard, Jojo.
Jojo, when I reach down to grab
the stone, I'll be off balance.
With my flank open, I'll be vulnerable.
Is that when you'll do it?
Is that when you'll try to kick me?
You'll attack me with your hamon,
even if it means the stone
disappears into the abyss.
You think your plan will work, Jojo?
Look there! Jojo!
You're right on the nose, Kaz!
Here it comes!
It's the kick you ordered! No!
Ah, he's used his legs to pick up
the stone right as Jojo kicked him.
He's going to get away with it.
I don't believe it!
Now, Kars, what's with that
ridiculously arrogant grin?
I mean, I'm the one who
should be smiling here.
I guess I should have
expected as much from you.
A trick like that really
isn't good enough to fool me.
My kick wasn't aimed at
your vulnerable flank,
but rather the snow, and it
worked just like a break.
What do you know?
Looks like I'm the one who
made the nice catch, not you.
Enjoy your trick, Kars!
Oh man, no way!
A blade from his foot!
Jojo!
He's falling viscars! What's happening?
Kars' blade is starting to
melt itself with my body!
It won't come out!
You son of a bitch!
It's 175 meters to the bottom!
Five seconds until impact! Damn!
Falling to my death with this guy?
No thank you!
Swinging Hamon!
He's so heavy!
Hamon goes through fluids easily, but ice
and snow are solid and impede the Hamon.
But water is trickling down the ice,
so the Hamon can use that
to flow around the solids.
Thus, it's working perfectly!
I don't care what you do,
the stone will be mine!
That's it, exactly.
That tenacity of yours, it's
what scares me the most.
I'm best at exploiting
my opponent's negligence,
so a tenacious foe is the
absolute worst for me to face.
Tenacity is the opposite of negligence.
It will be mine today!
More icicles up ahead!
Before I can do anything
I have to get this
blade out of my shoulder
oh wait I can just send
Hamon through the blade
and directly into Cars
take this as I thought I
knew you would try using my
blade against me just
for that it's into the
clip wall with you and
now no wait he's gonna use
that blade and cut me into
pieces Cars is waiting
for Jojo to rebound before
he starts cutting him
There's no way he can dodge that!
Now I'm going to take great
pleasure in slicing you in
half and picking up the stone
at the bottom of the abyss!
You!
Now you're not about to cut this, are you?
You wouldn't dare take the chance of
chopping the stone in half along with me!
I can use your own strength
against you by letting
your tenacity act as a
defensive measure for me!
Now eat this, Kars!
I'm on kick!
Damn!
He's trying to use the
fallen icicles as a rope.
He's clever, but they're
in a freefall, too.
He'll never reach the top!
In that case, allow me
to lend a hand! Hold on!
Huh?
Caesar!
Hey, nice timing, don't you think, Jojo?
What the hell's going on?
And what are you two, some kind of a team?
Fusing falling icicles
together to make a rescue rope?
I had nothing to do with that.
Only Jojo would try something
that colossally stupid.
It was predictable.
At least you were able
to think up a stupid
trick and then pull it
off in the nick of time.
I'm proud of you, Caesar.
What was that?
Nice, nice.
Real outstanding work, Caesarino. No.
And hey, if Lisa Lisa is up
there, give her a message.
I've got the red stone and it's safe.
I kept him from snatching it.
That was a close call.
All right, Caesar, you had
better pull him up now.
Now, my German compatriot,
your body is even more durable than
any of theirs could hope to be.
Listen, if you can stop with the
snobbery, maybe we can work together.
Mafia!
Jojo, you're a lucky one.
I'll let you hold the stone for
me for at least another day.
So,
this is Switzerland's famous San Moritz,
a winter sports hub often
referred to as Sun Valley.
Chic, relaxed, and sophisticated.
A resort that the wealthy
flock to during the holidays.
Even the cats look like
they're owned by actresses
and are pampered at all
the finest spas in Europe.
Aren't we fussy?
Not even a tiny glance for shrimp?
This little princess thinks
she's the center of the
universe but doesn't know a
thing about the world at all.
All right, then.
Would this smoked salmon suit
your snooty palate better?
There we go.
It seems I've found what you prefer.
That's it.
Reach for it.
Just a little bit higher now.
Stretch up just a little more there.
I gotcha now.
Aw, did I upset you?
Enjoy, you puny, pompous puffball.
That was pretty mean.
I don't know why I thought
it would be a good idea.
It's just because I'm really on edge.
We only have five days
until the ring dissolves,
and Cars is absolutely
serious about killing me.
I can feel the threats closing in.
They're all around.
I have to relax.
This is ridiculous.
I'm the one who's always saying you
can't sit around moping about stuff.
Jojo, what are you doing
just sitting there?
Get up out of that chair.
Come over here and look at this.
Right.
Be there in a second.
The building on top of that hill is
the address ACDC put on the package.
It looks like the abandoned
corpse of a shuttered hotel.
It would make a perfect hideout
for Kars during daylight hours.
Every doorway and window is boarded up.
No sunlight could get in there.
That's got to be it.
I'm sure Kars hides in
there during the day.
I bet he's just sitting inside
waiting for Wangu to show up.
All right.
So what is the plan?
That's a no-brainer.
We should attack now!
Yes, I agree.
Kars can't go outside as
long as the sun is up.
And that gives us a tremendous advantage.
What do you think?
Sorry, but I have to disagree with you.
You're looking at this wrong.
I think it's more dangerous
to attack when the sun is up.
Just think about it.
Kars has been living like
this for thousands of years.
He wouldn't have survived if he had
left himself defenseless during the day.
Oh, please!
Walking into his hideout and trying to
take him down right now would be suicidal.
I'm not going to do it.
It would be like a bug walking
into a spider's web on purpose.
Ha, come on.
Jojo, this isn't like you.
Are you scared or something?
I think I'm going to take
Sun Tzu's advice this time.
Only engage in a fight
when victory is assured.
Like I said, I'm not going in. Oh, yeah?
So you're chickening out?
I'm not afraid.
I'm just thinking straight.
I've got a cool head unlike you.
Caesar, we have to wait for
him to make his move first.
An assured victory is what you want.
Kars is all alone there.
It's him against all of us.
That's a Fortun advantage.
We have to strike now before Wamu
arrives cutting that in half. Calm down.
Don't go off all crazy now.
Try and keep your head together.
Just focus and think it through.
If we go now, he'll cut us to pieces.
You can't approach this half-cocked.
I am not half-cocked.
I'm gonna end this.
I am going to finally
finish the fight That
cut short the lives of
both of our grandfathers!
I'm gonna destroy her!
You're going to finish it?
Right!
And why bring our dead
grandfathers into this?
Who the hell cares?
Don't drag the dead into
your little drama, you moron!
What did you say to me?
Family you've never met and that came
long before your time doesn't mean crap!
It's just foolish!
Only a complete idiot would
die for something like that!
Caesar!
You watch your mouth!
JoJo!
Hey, what was that for?
A sucker punch!
Oh, it's on!
What the hell, Caesar?
What's wrong with you?
Just shut the hell up!
Caesar, stop it! Now!
You too, JoJo! Caesar!
You bastard, what's with you?
Have you completely lost it?
You're acting like some
kind of a madman Jojo,
I guess you won't ever
understand the concept of
family honor and inheriting
a battle like this Huh?
Enough, I'm going.
Caesar, Jojo is right,
it's far too dangerous.
We have no way of knowing what
might be waiting for us in there.
We'll wait for Kars to make his move.
That is an order, Caesar.
The only thing that matters now is
protecting the Red Stone of Asia.
No, Coach. I'm sorry.
I can't obey this time.
You know this is a matter
of blood and family honor.
It's a Zeppeli problem!
I just can't leave it unsettled when
I know exactly where Kars is hiding.
I can't sit here twirling my thumbs,
waiting for him to come to me!
What do we do?
Follow him and do whatever you
have to to stop him from entering,
even if it means using force.
Caesar, why are you doing this?
Why are you so damn grim and
hot-headed all of a sudden?
Why can't you be patient
and just wait a while?
You see, you've inadvertently touched
on a painful piece of his hidden past.
Although you didn't mean to,
you've hit upon a dark place where
he harbors his saddest secrets.
Caesar has a hidden past
What the hell could it be?
The roundabout.
The words will make you out and out.
I'll spend the day your way.
Call it morning driving through the sun.
And in and out the valley.
The music dance and sing.
They make the children really ring.
I spend the day your way.
Call it morning, driving through the sun.
And in and out the valley.
In and out around the lake.
Mountains come out of the sky.
And they'll stand there.
One mile over, we'll be
there and we'll see you.
Ten two summers, we'll be
there and laughing at you.
Twenty four and five
mile over, we'll see you.
I'll be there with you.
I feel like I did back then,
when I was naive and poor.
I'll use my viciousness
to destroy you! Very well.
You are worthy of death
at my hands, bubble user!